Hey , are you OK ?
Yeah .
You need some help ?
No .
[ man ] Annie ? What are you doing ?
I 'm fine , Dad .
What 's the matter ? What 's going on ?
Annie ?
[ phone rings ]
[ whimpers ] Dad ? Hi .
I love you .
I know . I know .
I just wanted you and Mum to know how much I love you .
Dad , I 'm sorry . I can be such a shit to you sometimes .
I don 't know why I do that .
Just know that I love you , OK ?
I just really love you both .
[ knocking ]
Hey , Jay .
- Hey . What 's up ? - Nothing .
Paul and Yara are here . We 're gonna watch a movie .
- Do you feel like it ? - Actually , I 'm going out tonight .
With that guy ?
I like him .
Me too .
I see you .
[ man on TV ] You will have access to event information
relative to the time and strength of the forthcoming atomic test .
[ man 2 ] What about it ?
[ man ] You will provide us with that information as soon as it is available .
[ man 2 ] I see .
[ woman laughs ] OK .
- [ man 2 ] You 're afraid of an overload . - Sounds good .
You can 't tap enough electricity wherever you get it from to control ...
a strong enough charge .
You are a clever man , Doctor . Perhaps too clever .
[ man 2 ] And what makes you think I 'll give you any information ?
[ man ] it is the only way you can save your own life when the time comes .
You will be transported to one of our platforms ...
What are you reading ?
The Idiot .
Is it any good ?
I don 't know yet . It 's about Paul .
Hey , Jay .
- Hey , Paul . - [ man 2 ] I 'll have to do as you say .
[ man ] You are lying , Doctor . Your only wish is to betray us .
- Stop . - [ man ] Call it what you like ...
- Hey , I have an idea . - What ?
[ farts ]
Oh ! It got away .
[ man ] You are an unwilling subject , Dr Martin .
[ man 2 ] What ? Who are you ?
[ woman ] What is the deal ?
You ever play the trade game ?
- No . What is that ? - It 's a people-watching game .
My sister and I used to play it when we were bored .
You 're bored right now ?
No . Shut up . Let me finish .
OK . How do you play ?
You start by watching the crowd , casually scope out the people around you .
OK .
Now , without telling me , pick a person that you 'd wanna trade places with .
It can be anyone for whatever reason .
OK , I got it .
Now I get two guesses to figure out who you picked
and why you 'd wanna trade places with them .
OK . Good luck .
That guy .
- Nope . - OK , then . Who 'd you pick ?
Him .
- The dad ? - No , the son .
I mean , how cool would that be to have your whole life ahead of you , you know ?
Come on . It 's not like you 're old . You 're 21 .
I know , but ... look at how happy that kid is .
Plus , at that age , you can go to the bathroom any time you want . Total freedom .
Yeah . He 's probably taking a shit right now .
Yeah , exactly . I could never get away with that .
[ plays jaunty music ]
OK , my turn .
OK .
OK , got it .
How about the girl in the yellow dress ?
Where ?
Right there .
- I don 't see her . - Right there .
Are you teasing me ?
I 'm sorry , I just ... I don 't see who you 're talking about .
Can we go ? I 'm sorry , I just ... I just don 't feel well .
Can we ... Can we go back to the car ?
Is there someone in there that made you wanna leave ?
Like an ex-girlfriend or something ?
You said you saw a girl with a yellow dress . Is that someone that you knew ?
No , I just felt sick . I feel better being outside .
Thanks for walking with me .
Mum knows you smoke .
Yeah , but she 'll cry if she actually sees it happening .
Or she 'll just steal your cigarettes .
How 's it going with Hugh ?
Good .
Mostly .
I don 't know . He was acting kind of weird last night .
Why ?
He said he wasn 't feeling well , but it seemed like something was on his mind .
Have you ... ?
No . No .
I know he wants to , but ... I don 't know . It seemed different last night .
Do I smell bad ?
Like cherry-coke banana nicotine .
- That 's my favourite flavour . - Mum will love it .
Let 's go back to the car .
It 's funny .
I used to daydream about being old enough to go on dates
and drive around with friends in their cars .
I had this image of myself holding hands with a really cute guy ...
listening to the radio , driving along some pretty road ...
up north maybe .
And the trees started to change colours .
It 's never about going anywhere , really .
It 's having some sort of freedom , I guess .
Now that we 're old enough , where the hell do we go ?
[ muffled ] Help !
Jay ?
You awake ?
I 'm sorry .
What are you doing ?
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
Don 't worry .
You 're not gonna believe me ,
but I need you to remember what I 'm saying .
OK ?
This thing
it 's gonna follow you .
Somebody gave it to me
and I passed it to you , back in the car .
It could look like someone you know
or it could be a stranger in a crowd .
Whatever helps it get close to you .
It can look like anyone .
But there 's only one of it .
Help .
Help !
And sometimes ... sometimes I think it looks like people you love
just to hurt you .
I see it . I see it .
No . No .
Who is it ?
You can get rid of it , OK ?
Just sleep with someone as soon as you can . Just pass it along .
If it kills you , it 'll come after me . Do you understand ?
What the fuck do you want ?
Jay , I 'm doing this to help you ,
just so you know it 's real .
Help ! Help me !
Never go into a place that doesn 't have more than one exit .
It 's very slow , but it 's not dumb .
Can I have some ?
Yeah .
[ Yara ] Hey , listen to this .
" I think that if one is faced with inevitable destruction ,
if a house is falling upon you , for instance ,
one must feel a great longing to sit down , close one 's eyes and wait , come what may . "
That 's why we 're drinking on the porch .
- Is your mum asleep already ? - Almost for sure .
She wakes up at 5 : 15 .
That would kill me .
So , where 's Jay at ?
On a date .
- Your turn . - Who is he ?
- Somebody new . - Of course .
- Your sister 's so pretty , it 's annoying . - It is annoying .
[ Paul ] Well , at least she 's nice .
Is everything OK ?
Don 't let it touch you .
Jay !
[ man introduces programme on TV ]
What happened ?
I don 't know .
Those people are such a mess .
[ officer ] It was consensual ?
Yeah .
And you 've never seen the woman before ?
No .
OK . Have you ever been to his home ?
I know where it is , but ... I 've never been inside .
He said he was embarrassed of where he lived .
[ woman ] Did she catch anything ?
[ woman 2 ] I don 't think so .
[ woman ] Oh , poor Jamie .
Apparently he used a fake name to rent the house in the city .
The police searched the place . They can 't find him .
[ woman 2 ] Oh , my God .
[ woman ] Breaks my heart , the things he said to her .
So weird and sick .
" I should have been a pair of ragged claws ,
scuttling across the floors of silent seas ,
and the afternoon , the evening , sleeps so peacefully ,
smoothed by long fingers , asleep , tired ,
or it malingers , stretched out on the floor , here beside you and me . "
" Should I , after tea and cakes and ices ,
have the strength to force the moment to its crisis ? "
" But though I have wept and fasted , wept and prayed ,
though I have seen my head grown slightly bald , brought in upon a platter ,
I am no prophet , and here 's no great matter . "
" I have seen the moment of my greatness flicker
and I have seen the eternal footmen hold my coat and snicker . "
" And , in short , I was afraid . "
" And would it have been worth it , after all ,
after the cups , the marmalade , the tea ,
among the porcelain , among some talk of you and me ,
would it have been worthwhile to have bitten off the matter with a smile ? "
" To have squeezed the universe into a ball . "
" To roll it toward some overwhelming question . "
" To say , " I am Lazarus , come from the dead ,
come back to tell you all , I shall tell you all " . "
" If one settling a pillow by her head should say ,
" That is not what I meant at all . That is not it at all " . "
Excuse me .
Excuse me !
Hello ?
Hello .
There was an old woman at school today .
And she was staring at me .
It was like she was following me .
- Did you know her ? - No , but she freaked me out .
I didn 't go back to class .
Did she say something to you ?
Hugh told me that he passed it on to me .
That something was gonna follow me .
[ Kelly ] That 's all bullshit , Jamie .
Yeah , I know .
What exactly is supposed to be following you ?
I don 't know .
- [ Kelly ] You should tell Mum what you saw . - No .
Well , Jay , I 'm worried about you .
I could stay over tonight if it would make you feel any better .
[ both ] No .
- Just on the couch or something . - No .
Maybe just on the couch .
You should be more worried about waking up and finding Paul humping your leg .
Um ... I 'm choosing to ignore these insults to my character .
Just keep your door locked .
Look , I 'm gonna stay up all night and keep an eye out for anything weird .
Nothing 's gonna happen , OK ?
[ man on TV ] Almost sounds like a girl .
[ man 2 ] A girl ? Perhaps .
Or a monster .
- [ man 2 ] Andre ! Andre ! - Stop teasing him . He 's in love .
[ man laughs ]
[ man on TV ] How much time before we get there ?
- [ man 2 ] Who knows ? - At least we know they 're alive .
[ man 2 ] Let 's hope they stay that way .
Commander , look there .
I can 't sleep , not in there .
That 's OK . Sleep here .
- [ man 2 ] He hit us ! He 's turning around ! - Maybe not .
[ man 2 ] We 're in for it now . He knows we 're here .
Here he comes .
Don 't miss , Andre .
[ man ] Open hallow . We 'll submerge .
[ narrator ] When we were forced to submerge , even though we had killed the flying reptile ,
because of the damage the creature ...
Are you OK ?
Everything 's gonna be cool .
It 's funny . I haven 't spent the night over here since we were kids .
There 's a reason for that .
Shut up . I 'm serious . I 'm ...
It 's cool spending time with you .
Yeah .
[ man on TV ] Behind you !
You were my first kiss , you know .
I know .
Was I not yours ?
No , uh ... you were .
And then you kissed Kelly .
She told me .
You kissed two sisters . That 's kind of gross .
Do you remember the time that we found those porno magazines
in the alley behind Barry 's Pizza ?
Yeah .
- We were such stupid kids . - Ridiculous .
Yeah , we 're all sitting out on Greg 's front lawn
with a dozen dirty magazines just sprawled out everywhere .
- And we 're laughing . - We didn 't even realise how bad it was .
Oh , and Greg 's mum , remember her face
when she came out and saw us reading that shit ?
And she scooped it up so fast . And then she called my mum .
Kelly and I got the sex ed talk the next day .
- I got one too . - [ window smashes ]
- What the fuck ? - Go look .
There 's a broken window in the kitchen , but there 's no one there .
- Are you sure ? - Yeah .
I mean , whoever broke it must have run away .
Maybe we should call the police .
I 'm gonna go wake up your sister . She should call .
[ creepy music on TV ]
[ screams ]
- [ Kelly knocks on door ] Jay ? - [ Paul ] Jay , can you open the door ?
- It 's in the house . - [ Kelly ] What 's going on ?
[ Paul ] There 's nothing in the house , Jay .
I saw it .
- [ Kelly ] Open the door , OK ? - It 's in the kitchen .
[ Paul ] I 'm not gonna let anything happen to you .
Open the door and we 'll figure this out . There 's nothing out here .
Get in .
Jay , why don 't you sit down ?
I need water . Oh , my God , I need water .
- [ Kelly ] OK , I 'll get you some . - No , stay here !
There 's something wrong with me .
[ Paul ] Look , somebody broke the window . That really happened .
Well , I saw a girl in the kitchen .
Jay , I love you .
- You 're OK . - You don 't believe me .
[ knock on door ]
[ Kelly ] Mum ?
Mum , is that you ?
- No , it 's me . - Yara ?
Yeah .
Don 't open the door .
[ Kelly ] See ? Everything 's OK .
[ screams ]
Jay !
Jay ! What are you doing ?
[ music plays on car radio ]
[ Paul ] Hey , Jay , wait !
Jay !
[ Paul ] Jay !
[ Kelly ] You could have hurt yourself . What are you doing ?
[ Jay sobs ]
I 'm scared .
Me too . But we 'll figure it out .
You can 't tell mum , cos she 'll freak out and she won 't believe me .
I know . It 's OK .
What are you running from ?
Do you see that ?
I do . It 's ... It 's a person .
- Greg ? - What the hell 's going on ? You OK ?
- Someone broke into their house . - Shit . Did you call the police ?
- I don 't wanna go home . - Where do you wanna go ?
I ... I need to find him .
The person who broke into your house ?
No .
Hugh ?
What did he really do to you ?
OK .
Are you leaving ?
No , I 'm getting my car . Someone 's gotta drive , right ?
[ screams ]
God .
Hey , come look at this .
What ?
Is this him ?
[ Paul ] You recognise the jacket ?
[ Jay ] Lawson High School .
Somebody 's gotta know his real name .
[ man ] Hello , students . It 's time for your afternoon announcements .
Attention all girls interested in playing club lacrosse this spring .
There will be an informational meeting held in the LT431 room right after school today .
Final reminder for all wrestlers .
Please hand in your permission forms to Mr Dwiggens today .
Also your banquet is this Sunday at 3pm here at the high school .
It 's time again for the high school musical ,
this year starting at 7pm to 9 : 30 a show ,
and another performance tomorrow at 2pm and 7pm .
Tickets will be $ 5 for students and $ 7 for adults .
Hope you all have a great weekend and we 'll see you here on Monday .
[ school bell rings ]
- [ Paul ] Did they know ? - Yep .
- His real name is Jeff . - Not Hugh ?
- [ Greg ] Jeff Redmond . - Do we tell the police ?
[ Jay ] No .
[ rings doorbell ]
Hello .
Hi . Um ... Is Jeff here ?
Yeah . Yeah , he is . Um , do you wanna come in ?
Yeah .
Your friends ?
Look , even though it 's following you , I can still see it .
It 's not done with me either , OK ?
And like I told , all you can do is pass it along to someone else .
- What the fuck are you talking about ? - Look , she can do the same thing I did .
I mean , it should be easy for her . She 's a girl . Any guy would be with you .
Sleep with someone else and tell them to do the same thing . Maybe it 'll never come back .
This isn 't real , I ... I swear to you . This is just some fucked-up game .
Look , I 'm not safe either , OK ?
We shouldn 't even be in the same place . You guys need to get the fuck out of here .
Hey , watch it .
If it kills her , it gets me
and goes straight down the line to whoever started it .
Jay ... I 'm sorry .
I wasn 't trying to hurt you , OK ? Someone did this to me too , OK ?
[ Jay ] Who did it to you ?
[ Jeff ] I met a girl at a bar .
It was a one-night stand . I ... I don 't even remember her name .
I think that 's where it came from .
[ Greg ] Jeff , I don 't believe you .
And while she might ,
I think you 're a fucking liar and what you 're doing to her is some fucked-up shit .
Do you guys see that girl right there ?
- Uh-huh . - Yes .
Yeah .
OK .
OK , good .
Jay , listen , wherever you are , it 's somewhere walking straight for you .
But it is walking .
If you drive far enough , you can buy yourself some time to think ,
decide if you wanna give it to someone else .
[ snores ]
Um , Greg ?
- [ Greg ] Yeah . - Your mum 's not gonna freak out ?
She won 't even know .
It 's really nice of you .
[ Greg ] I love coming up here .
My dad , he , um ... he used to take me hunting a couple of times a year .
It 's not like super nice , but ... it 's cool .
Have you thought about what he said ?
[ Jay ] What ?
Maybe passing it on ?
I don 't know .
[ gunshot ]
It sucks sticking around when everyone 's gone , huh ?
It 's a bit lonely .
I 'm right across the street , you know .
I remember .
I guess I should have been nicer to you .
You guys should get in the water !
You want to ?
Maybe in a little bit .
Come on .
Oh , my God ! Help me !
Jay , what is it ?
[ Jay ] Help !
Help me !
[ Yara ] What are you doing ?
[ Kelly ] Jay , please !
[ Greg ] Stop shooting !
[ banging on door ]
Oh , God !
- What the hell are you guys doing ? - Don 't open the door !
- What 'd you do to the door ? - We didn 't do that .
- It 's trying to come in ! - There 's nothing out here !
Yes , there is .
Greg ?
Greg , are you OK ?
[ Yara ] Jay , what do you see ?
[ Kelly ] Jay ! Jay , wait !
[ Greg ] Hey , that 's my fucking car !
[ footsteps ]
Have you seen it ?
Nothing .
I 'm waiting , looking .
It 's been three days . I don 't think it 's coming .
You believe me , right ?
You 're not just playing along ?
No , I ... I believe you . I just ... I just don 't think it 's following me .
Isn 't that a good thing ?
Yeah .
[ newsreader ] We are following a four-alarm fire that is happening right now .
The crews are battling that on Detroit 's west side
and we 're gonna get out to Chopper Eight , Rich Kensington .
What are you seeing right now ? Fill us in on what you 're seeing .
[ Rich ] Yes , just on scene to this one , guys .
It 's just north of I-96 , along the service drive ,
I-96 westbound service drive , just before you get to the outer drive ...
Hey .
How are you guys ?
[ Kelly ] OK .
How 's , uh ... How 's Jay ?
Not great .
Have you seen anything ?
No .
Is ... Is it cool if I go in ?
I don 't think so . She doesn 't wanna open her door .
She 's just hiding in there .
I thought she 'd be doing better .
I can have her call you later ?
Yeah . OK .
You really haven 't seen anything ?
- Nope . - She didn 't make it up .
We 'll know sooner or later , right ?
That chair broke in mid-air .
I mean , something knocked me over , and the door didn 't break on its own .
Look , something happened . But it 's not what she thinks , OK ?
What do you think it was , then ?
I 'll see you guys .
- [ Kelly ] Bye , Greg . - [ Yara ] Bye .
[ ringing tone ]
[ Greg ] Hi . You 've reached Greg . Leave a message .
Greg ! Open the door , Greg !
[ banging ]
Greg , watch out !
[ banging continues ]
Greg , don 't open the door !
What the fuck , Mum ?
[ sobs ]
[ distant music playing ]
[ knocking ]
- Who is it ? - Paul .
Hang on .
It 's gonna be here sooner or later .
You could pass it on .
You did once .
I shouldn 't have .
I could ...
No .
I liked you too , you know .
Why 'd you pick Greg ?
I thought he 'd be OK .
He wasn 't scared .
We slept together in high school . It wasn 't a big deal .
I wanna help .
Do you ?
Yeah , I do .
- Jay ? - Yeah ?
Do you trust me ?
Do you remember where we were the first time we kissed ?
- Know where to go ? - I know how to get there , you 'll see .
I haven 't been to the pool since I was 14 .
Who brought you there ?
- OK . - That 's where I had my first beer .
I threw up the whole night .
- [ Yara ] Into the pool ? - [ Kelly ] No . Outside the car .
- [ Paul ] And in the car . - [ Kelly ] Paul used to pee in it .
- [ Yara ] Ew . That 's disgusting . - [ Paul ] Whatever . There 's chlorine .
When I was a little girl , my parents wouldn 't allow me to go south of Eight Mile .
And I didn 't even know what that meant until I got a little older
and I started realising that that 's where the city started and the suburbs ended .
And I used to think about how shitty and weird that was .
I mean , I had to ask permission to go to the state fair
with my best friend and her parents
only because it was a few blocks past the border .
My mum said the same thing .
How long do you think it 'll be ?
I don 't know . Hours , I bet .
[ thunder ]
[ Jay ] Oh , my God .
It just walked in the room . It 's right there .
- [ Paul ] It 's here ? - Right there !
[ Kelly ] Jay , what do you see ?
I don 't wanna tell you .
[ Paul ] Jay , I need you to point at it , OK ?
Keep your finger aimed at it so we can see where it is .
Is it getting in the water ?
It 's just standing there staring at me .
- It 's moving . - [ Yara ] What 's it doing ?
[ Jay ] It 's walking . It 's just walking .
- Paul , I wanna get out . - No ! Just wait for it to get in .
No , I don 't wanna do this . I just wanna get out !
- [ Paul ] What the fuck ? - [ Kelly ] Jay !
[ Paul ] Get out of there !
- [ Kelly ] She 's gonna get electrocuted ! - [ Paul ] No , it didn 't work !
- [ Kelly ] You OK ? - Yeah .
- It didn 't work . - [ Kelly ] Thank God .
- [ Kelly ] Jay , look out ! - [ screams ]
- [ Kelly ] Oh , my God , somebody help her ! - [ Yara ] What do we do ?
[ Yara ] What the hell is going on ?
[ Paul ] Jay , just keep pointing at it !
[ Jay ] It 's right there !
Where is it ?
Watch out ! Don 't get too close ! It 's right there !
[ Kelly ] Yara !
Where ?
Here ?
- Here ? - Right there !
Where is it ?
- [ Paul ] Jay ! - Come on , Jay ! Hurry !
- Give me your hand . - Come on , come on , come on !
Jay !
[ gunshots ]
[ Paul ] Jay ?
Do you see it ? Is it still down there ?
[ thunder ]
Do you feel any different ?
Do you ?
No .
" When there 's torture , there is pain and wounds , physical agony ,
and all this distracts the mind from mental suffering
so that one is tormented by the wounds until the moment of death . "
" And the most terrible agony may not be in the wounds themselves
but in knowing for certain that within an hour , then within ten minutes ,
then within half a minute , now , at this very instant ,
your soul will leave your body and you will no longer be a person
and that , this is certain , the worst thing is that it is certain . "
- ------ OCR 'd by ProperSRT - ------